Secure your remote access communication with the Shrew Soft VPN Client!

HOME : PRIVACY POLICY

### What information do we collect?

* * *

We collect information from you when you register an account on our web site, submit information using our contact form, or make a purchase from our online store.

When registering an account on our web site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: first name, last name, email address and a user password. When making purchases, you may be asked to enter additional details for the purpose of payment processing. Card holder data such as credit card numbers and/or card security codes are not stored on our system. Any other information that is required to process a payment will only be retained on our system until the sale has been completed. You may, however, browse our web site without registering an account.

### What do we use your information for?

* * *

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  

* To personalize your experience.
* To improve our website.
* To improve customer service.

Shrew Soft may also send periodic emails when an account has been registered on our web site and the user has requested updates or information related to a specific topic. If at any time the user would like to stop receiving emails related to a specific topic, the account settings can be easily updated from their account preferences page on our web site. An account email address may be used to respond to inquiries, other requests and/or questions.

### How do we protect your information?

* * *

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

### Do we use cookies?

* * *

Yes. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, process user purchases and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. One of the services that we use to gather web site statistics is Google Analytics. If you have questions regarding this service, please visit the following URL for more information ...  

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

* * *

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is necessary to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

* * *

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date. The last update to this policy was made on June 5, 2013.

### Your Consent

* * *

By using our site, you consent to the privacy policy presented on this web page.

### Contacting Us

* * *

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.  
  
Shrew Soft Inc.  
PO Box 42184  
Austin, TX 78704

[HOME](https://www.shrew.net/home) | [SOFTWARE](https://www.shrew.net/software) | [DOWNLOAD](https://www.shrew.net/download) | [SHOP](https://www.shrew.net/shop) | [SUPPORT](https://www.shrew.net/support) | [CONTACT](https://www.shrew.net/contact) | [ABOUT](https://www.shrew.net/about) | [PRIVACY](https://www.shrew.net/privacy)     © 2013 Shrew Soft Inc.
